

Visual finesse and better experiences drive my work wagon. The challenge to play in the hybrid space, an infusion of design and technology is exciting and fulfilling. My specialities include Human Computer Interaction, Design Research, Data Visualisation, User Experience Design, and Story-boarding."

EXPERIENCE

PhonePe (Flipkart), Bangalore, India User Experience Designer, Feb 2018-Present

Hotstar (Star India), Mumbai, India User Experience Design (Contract), Jan 2018

Microsoft, IDC, Hyderabad, India User Experience Design Intern, Jul 2017-Dec 2017

Deloitte-USI, Bangalore, India Business Analyst - Cyber Security, Jul 2014-Jul 2015

General Electric, Bangalore, India Software Developer Intern, Jan 2014-Jun 2014

IBM, Bangalore, India Software Developer Intern, Jul 2013-Aug 2013

College Editorial Board MIT, Manipal, India
Creative Head of council of 40 students, 2013-2014

PUBLICATIONS

"Community Based System Design for Indian Railways in the Context of Senior Citizens" - Interact 2017, IIT-Bombay - Springer

"Introducing New Age To ICH: Revering Matters Of Significance" - IndiaHCl2016, IIT-Bombay - ACM

EDUCATION

Hochschule für Technik und Wirtschaft, Berlin, Germany (Exchange Student) Communication Design, Winter 2017

National Institute of Design, Bangalore, India M.Des in Information Design, 2015-2017

Manipal Institute of Technology, MAHE, Manipal, India B.Tech in Computer Science, 2010-2014 | 8.6 CGPA

St. Michael's High School, Patna, India CBSE, 1998-2010 | XIIth 92%, Xth 95%

ACHIEVEMENTS

UXIndia 2017 - Student Gold Award

Adobe Design Achievement Awards 2017 - Semifinalist

Information is Beautiful Awards 2017 - Longlist

D'Vibes Deloitte Annual Fest 2015 - Best Logo

Microsoft Windows App Hackathon, Manipal, 2013 - Second Prize

Revels - Manipal Fest 2010-14 - Awards in Fine Arts & Cartooning

Techniche, IIT-G 2010 - School Student Shortlist

Best Michaelite, 2010 - Excellence for 12 years at school

GOOD AT

Sketch
Principle
Adobe XD
Photoshop
Illustrator
Flinto
Story-Boarding
HTML/CSS
Javascript

Prototyping

INTERESTS

User Experience
User Interface
Design Research
Information
Architecture
Data Visualisation
Graphic Design

SUMMING IT UP!



REACH OUT AT

E: atul_ku@nid.edu myspace.atul@gmail.com

P: +91 9742721604

W: www.atulkr.com linkedin.com/in/atul-kr be.net/_atul_kumar